[Disclaimer: This series is entirely fictional and solely for entertainment purposes
[تنويه: هذه السلسلة خيالية بالكامل ولأغراض الترفيه فقط]
with no association or reference to any individuals, places, or events;
دون أي ارتباط أو إشارة إلى أي أفراد أو أماكن أو أحداث؛
there may be inappropriate behaviors and vulgarity based on the character's persona;
قد تتضمن بعض الأعمال سلوكيات غير لائقة وألفاظاً بذيئة بناءً على شخصية البطل؛
viewer discretion is advised]
يُنصح بمشاهدة المحتوى بحذر.
Did you smell something?
هل شممت رائحة ما؟
Omelet?
أومليت؟
It's the smell of our memories.
إنها رائحة ذكرياتنا.
Wear blue tomorrow.
ارتدي اللون الأزرق غداً.
I want us to wear matching shirts.
أريد أن نرتدي قمصانًا متطابقة.
My friend is quite charismatic.
صديقي يتمتع بشخصية جذابة للغاية.
Apart from the prophecy stones,
وبغض النظر عن أحجار النبوءة،
are you also a master of love potions?
هل أنت أيضاً خبير في تحضير جرعات الحب؟
Haven't you told him yet
ألم تخبره بعد؟
that you're not the real sweetheart?
أنك لست الحبيب الحقيقي؟
Aren't you gonna be a little humble,
ألن تتحلى ببعض التواضع؟
Prince Charming?
الأمير الساحر؟
If I bow down,
إذا انحنيت،
will you have me?
هل تقبلني؟
Is Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master, here?
هل ريت، سيد حجر النبوءة، موجود هنا؟
We've arrived.
لقد وصلنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Are you back at your place?
هل عدت إلى منزلك؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Are you worried about me or afraid your bar is missing a fortune teller?
هل أنت قلق عليّ أم تخشى أن حانتك تفتقر إلى عرافة؟
Do you have any idea
هل لديك أي فكرة؟
who was here looking for you
من كان هنا يبحث عنك؟
after you left?
بعد مغادرتك؟
Who?
من؟
The real one
الحقيقي
has come back to claim what's his.
لقد عاد ليطالب بما هو ملكه.
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫هل هي مجرد صدفة؟♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫أم أن القدر هو الذي يقرر؟♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫هل هناك من يرسم كل هذه الخطوط من الأعلى؟♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫ أم أنك تلعب دور خاطبة متخفية؟ ♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫ ماذا لو تحركت النجوم من مكانها؟ ♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫خارج عن المألوف قليلاً،♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫هل ستظل مداراتنا متطابقة؟♫
♫Try answering (if) your world will cross with mine♫
♫حاول الإجابة (إذا) سيتقاطع عالمك مع عالمي♫
♫Though the destiny between us is differently defined♫
♫على الرغم من أن المصير بيننا مُحدد بشكل مختلف♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫وأعتقد أن لحبنا قوة♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫أؤمن بحبنا♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line where they should be♫
♫سيعيد ترتيب النجوم إلى الخط الذي ينبغي أن تكون عليه♫
- Here you go. - Wait, that's Pitcha,
- تفضل. - لحظة، هذا بيتشا،
the one who trained in Korea since childhood.
الشخص الذي تدرب في كوريا منذ طفولته.
Oh, the boy who got his dream crushed and didn't debut?
أوه، ذلك الفتى الذي تحطمت أحلامه ولم يظهر لأول مرة؟
He just got injured; otherwise, he'd have already debuted.
لقد أصيب للتو؛ وإلا لكان قد شارك لأول مرة بالفعل.
Who is that?
من ذاك؟
The one who's on the news for debuting as a K-pop idol.
الشخص الذي يتصدر الأخبار لظهوره الأول كنجم في موسيقى البوب ​​الكورية.
What? Are you a K-pop stan?
ماذا؟ هل أنت من محبي موسيقى الكيبوب؟
I went to school with him when I was a child.
ذهبت إلى المدرسة معه عندما كنت طفلاً.
I remember
أتذكر
that he was teased about
أنه تعرض للسخرية بسبب
being Business graduate Itthi's sweetheart.
كونها حبيبة إيثي، خريجة إدارة الأعمال.
Oh!
أوه!
- That handsome poser with a rich daddy? - Yes!
- ذلك الوسيم المتصنع ذو الأب الثري؟ - نعم!
- There you go. - Right, I know who he is.
- ها هو ذا. - صحيح، أعرف من هو.
Go say hi.
اذهب وسلّم عليّ.
No way.
مستحيل.
He's not gonna remember me.
لن يتذكرني.
Pitch...
يقذف...
Do you have a table reserved?
هل لديك طاولة محجوزة؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Is Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master, here?
هل ريت، سيد حجر النبوءة، موجود هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
What do I do if I want my fortune read by Master Ritt?
ماذا أفعل إذا أردت أن يقرأ لي السيد ريت طالعي؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Why? Is he fully booked?
لماذا؟ هل جدوله ممتلئ؟
He was here, but...
كان هنا، لكن...
he just left a minute ago.
لقد غادر قبل دقيقة واحدة فقط.
Uh, Mister... Do you want your fortune read, Pitcha?
آه، سيدي... هل تريد قراءة طالعك يا بيتشا؟
You'll have to wait until tomorrow, but I'll book you in for the first slot.
سيتعين عليك الانتظار حتى الغد، لكنني سأحجز لك موعداً في أول فترة زمنية.
My name is Ployplern.
اسمي بلويبليرن.
I'm your fan.
أنا من معجبيك.
Uh, so...
حسنًا...
- Is your ankle all better? - Then, I'd better come back tomorrow.
- هل كاحلك بخير الآن؟ - إذن، من الأفضل أن أعود غداً.
What time should I be here?
متى يجب أن أكون هنا؟
Around 10 or 11 PM.
حوالي الساعة العاشرة أو الحادية عشرة مساءً.
Okay, thank you.
حسناً، شكراً لك.
Hold up.
أصمد.
Since you're already here at Magic Move,
بما أنك موجود بالفعل هنا في ماجيك موف،
would you give us the honor of serving you?
هل تتفضلون بمنحنا شرف خدمتكم؟
If you're here alone, you can take the bar.
إذا كنت هنا بمفردك، يمكنك أخذ البار.
My sister and I will take care of you.
أنا وأختي سنعتني بك.
I'm good.
أنا بخير.
Come on.
تعال.
Consider this a private fan meeting for her.
اعتبروا هذا لقاءً خاصاً مع معجبيها.
This girl
هذه الفتاة
is your No.1 fan.
هو معجبك الأول.
Let's do it tomorrow.
لنفعل ذلك غداً.
Today is fine. Come on.
اليوم جيد. هيا.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
And I...
وأنا...
will prepare a very special drink for you.
سأقوم بإعداد مشروب مميز جداً لك.
So...
لذا...
you can drink, right?
يمكنك الشرب، أليس كذلك؟
Or do you have to ask for your company's permission first?
أم هل يجب عليك طلب إذن شركتك أولاً؟
If you're concerned that someone might take a photo in secret,
إذا كنت قلقًا من أن يقوم شخص ما بالتقاط صورة سرًا،
- I can serve your drink in an opaque glass. - I can drink.
- يمكنني تقديم مشروبك في كأس زجاجي معتم. - يمكنني الشرب.
Please wait just a second.
انتظر لحظة من فضلك.
Are you hot? I can turn up the A/C for you.
هل تشعر بالحر؟ يمكنني تشغيل المكيف من أجلك.
I'm good.
أنا بخير.
The restroom is that way.
دورة المياه من هناك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Uh...
أوه...
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
Would you like any appetizers? Or maybe a whole meal to fill you up?
هل ترغب في بعض المقبلات؟ أو ربما وجبة كاملة لتشبعك؟
The kitchen is actually closed, but I can reopen it
المطبخ مغلق بالفعل، لكن يمكنني إعادة فتحه.
since I'm the owner's little sister.
لأنني أخت المالك الصغرى.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
And what's your name again?
وما اسمك مرة أخرى؟
It's Ployplern.
إنه بوليبليرن.
You can call me Ploy or Plern. Both are fine.
يمكنك مناداتي بـ "بلوي" أو "بليرن". كلاهما مناسب.
Can I have a photo with you?
هل يمكنني التقاط صورة معك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Let's do a selfie. Front camera photos mean you're close.
لنلتقط صورة سيلفي. الصور الملتقطة بالكاميرا الأمامية تعني أنك قريب.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let me take it.
دعني آخذه.
Ready?
مستعد؟
Pure, don't photobomb me! We're taking a two-shot!
بيور، لا تفسدي الصورة! سنلتقط صورة ثنائية!
The more the merrier.
كلما زاد العدد كان ذلك أفضل.
All set?
هل كل شيء جاهز؟
There you go.
تفضل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Here you go,
ها أنت ذا،
our special recipe.
وصفتنا الخاصة.
This cocktail hasn't been named yet.
لم يتم تسمية هذا الكوكتيل بعد.
If you like it,
إذا أعجبك،
may I name it after you?
هل لي أن أسميها باسمك؟
I'd rather not.
أفضّل عدم القيام بذلك.
You know, my sister here
كما تعلمون، أختي هنا
is your biggest fan.
هو أكبر معجب بك.
She's been keeping up with your updates as if she were the news agency herself.
لقد كانت تتابع آخر أخبارك كما لو كانت هي وكالة الأنباء نفسها.
Right, I forgot to introduce myself.
صحيح، لقد نسيت أن أقدم نفسي.
My name is Pure.
اسمي بيور.
I'm the owner of this bar.
أنا صاحب هذا البار.
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
I'm Pitcha.
أنا بيتشا.
You don't have to introduce yourself.
لستَ مضطراً لتقديم نفسك.
Everyone here knows you.
الجميع هنا يعرفك.
This is the first time I've met you,
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي ألتقي بك فيها،
yet it feels like I see you every day.
لكني أشعر وكأنني أراك كل يوم.
This girl loves watching your videos.
هذه الفتاة تحب مشاهدة فيديوهاتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
So when are you going back to Korea?
متى ستعود إلى كوريا؟
It's pushed off indefinitely.
تم تأجيله إلى أجل غير مسمى.
But your leg...
لكن ساقك...
looks fine.
يبدو جيداً.
Oh, so...
أوه، إذن...
you want to get your fortune told because of this, don't you?
أنت تريد أن تعرف طالعك بسبب هذا، أليس كذلك؟
I heard my friends in Thailand talking about it,
سمعت أصدقائي في تايلاند يتحدثون عن ذلك،
so I thought I might give it a try.
لذلك فكرت في أن أجرب ذلك.
So you're a victim of social media trends.
إذن أنت ضحية لاتجاهات وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي.
Pure, isn't it good enough that he's here?
نقي، أليس وجوده هنا كافياً؟
I'm booking you for the first appointment.
سأحجز لك موعدك الأول.
I'll get it sorted.
سأقوم بحل المشكلة.
Then...
ثم...
I'd better get going.
من الأفضل أن أذهب.
I'll be back tomorrow.
سأعود غداً.
You can go ahead and get me the bill. Is a bank transfer alright?
يمكنك إحضار الفاتورة لي. هل التحويل البنكي مناسب؟
It's fine.
لا بأس.
This one is on the house
هذا مجاني
since you've given us the honor of gracing our bar.
بما أنكم منحتمونا شرف التواجد في حانتنا.
Thank you, then.
شكراً لك إذن.
Then... I'll see you tomorrow.
إذن... أراك غداً.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Was he even real? Am I dreaming?!
هل كان حقيقياً أصلاً؟ هل أنا أحلم؟!
He stepped foot into our bar!
لقد دخل إلى حانتنا!
There's more to freak out about.
هناك ما هو أكثر من ذلك يدعو للقلق.
I can smell chaos ensuing.
أستطيع أن أشم رائحة الفوضى التي ستحدث.
We've arrived.
لقد وصلنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Are you holding up alright?
هل أنت بخير؟
Do you want me to walk you upstairs?
هل تريدين أن أرافقكِ إلى الطابق العلوي؟
I'm alright.
أنا بخير.
It's not like I'm drunk.
ليس الأمر كما لو أنني ثمل.
Not drunk?
لستَ ثملاً؟
You fell asleep and snored so loudly.
لقد غفوتَ وشخرتَ بصوتٍ عالٍ.
Drunk? I'm not drunk.
سكران؟ لست سكراناً.
I saw how much you drank,
رأيت كم شربت،
and you still insist you're not.
وما زلت تصر على أنك لست كذلك.
I'm telling you that I'm not.
أقول لك إني لست كذلك.
Why are you doing this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Doing what?
ماذا تفعل؟
Making me fall in love.
يجعلني أقع في الحب.
Is it working?
هل يعمل؟
Do you want me to walk you to your place?
هل تريدني أن أوصلك إلى منزلك؟
Hah.
هاه.
I know
أنا أعرف
what you're thinking about doing up there.
ما الذي تفكر في فعله هناك؟
Walking you to your place, of course.
سأوصلك إلى منزلك، بالطبع.
No, no, no.
لا، لا، لا.
I'm not falling for that.
لن أنخدع بذلك.
Falling for what?
الوقوع في حب ماذا؟
Who actually started it?
من بدأ الأمر فعلاً؟
I'd better go.
من الأفضل أن أذهب.
Hold up.
أصمد.
When do you want me to pick you up?
متى تريدني أن آتي لأخذك؟
To where?
إلى أين؟
To the university, of course.
إلى الجامعة بالطبع.
I'm not going.
لن أذهب.
I'll work on my assignments at my place tomorrow.
سأعمل على واجباتي في منزلي غداً.
Then...
ثم...
I'll keep you company.
سأبقى معك.
Do you even have time?
هل لديك وقت أصلاً؟
I sure do.
بالتأكيد.
I promise
أعدك
I'll sit completely still.
سأجلس بلا حراك تماماً.
You won't even notice I'm there.
لن تلاحظ حتى وجودي هناك.
Mm.
مم.
Before bed,
قبل النوم،
send me a message, okay?
أرسل لي رسالة، حسناً؟
Got it.
فهمتها.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Mm.
مم.
Are you back at your place?
هل عدت إلى منزلك؟
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Are you worried about me or afraid your bar is missing a fortune teller?
هل أنت قلق عليّ أم تخشى أن حانتك تفتقر إلى عرافة؟
Do you have any idea
هل لديك أي فكرة؟
who was here looking for you
من كان هنا يبحث عنك؟
after you left?
بعد مغادرتك؟
How am I supposed to know that?
كيف لي أن أعرف ذلك؟
Who?
من؟
The real one
الحقيقي
has come back to claim what's his.
لقد عاد ليطالب بما هو ملكه.
Where were you so late?
أين كنت في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
Outside, Mom.
بالخارج يا أمي.
So where exactly?
إذن أين تحديداً؟
I was meeting some friends.
كنتُ سأقابل بعض الأصدقاء.
Do you have another doctor's appointment tomorrow?
هل لديك موعد آخر مع الطبيب غداً؟
Not until next week.
ليس قبل الأسبوع القادم.
Is your leg doing fine now?
هل ساقك بخير الآن؟
It is, Mom.
نعم يا أمي.
What are you doing out here? Why haven't you gone to bed?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟ لماذا لم تذهب إلى النوم؟
I saw that you weren't home yet, so I was worried.
رأيت أنك لم تعد إلى المنزل بعد، لذلك كنت قلقاً.
Then, please go to bed.
ثم، من فضلك اذهب إلى النوم.
I'll be taking a shower before bed.
سأستحم قبل النوم.
If your leg is doing fine now,
إذا كانت ساقك بخير الآن،
you should get back to your dance practices sometimes.
يجب عليك العودة إلى تدريبات الرقص الخاصة بك من حين لآخر.
Yes, Mom.
نعم يا أمي.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Oh, Itthi.
أوه، إيثي.
Where are you heading out to?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
How about a meal first?
ما رأيك بتناول وجبة أولاً؟
I have something to attend to.
لديّ أمرٌ عليّ القيام به.
Hm?
همم؟
I'm heading out now.
سأغادر الآن.
This early in the morning?
في هذا الوقت المبكر من الصباح؟
Right?
يمين؟
Alright, once the incense burns out, take down the offerings.
حسناً، بمجرد أن ينطفئ البخور، انزع القرابين.
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫هل هي مجرد صدفة؟♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫أم أن القدر هو الذي يقرر؟♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫هل هناك من يرسم كل هذه الخطوط من الأعلى؟♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫ أم أنك تلعب دور خاطبة متخفية؟ ♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫ ماذا لو تحركت النجوم من مكانها؟ ♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫خارج عن المألوف قليلاً،♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫هل ستظل مداراتنا متطابقة؟♫
♫Try answering if your world will cross with mine♫
♫ حاول الإجابة عما إذا كان عالمك سيتقاطع مع عالمي ♫
♫Though the destiny between us is differently defined♫
♫على الرغم من أن المصير بيننا مُحدد بشكل مختلف♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫أعتقد أن حبنا سيغيرنا♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫يا قدر، أعد كتابة النبوءات♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫حتى لو كانوا ضد مصيرنا♫
♫(But we're gonna try… try… try!)♫
♫(لكننا سنحاول... سنحاول... سنحاول!)♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫وأعتقد أن لحبنا قوة♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫أؤمن بحبنا♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line where they should be♫
♫سيعيد ترتيب النجوم إلى الخط الذي ينبغي أن تكون عليه♫
♫(And we're gonna try… try… try!)♫
♫(وسنحاول... نحاول... نحاول!)♫
Hey,
يا،
are you almost done
هل انتهيت تقريباً؟
so you can finally get in the pool with me?
إذن يمكنك أخيرًا النزول إلى المسبح معي؟
Quit bugging!
كفى إزعاجاً!
I'm trying to focus on my work here.
أحاول التركيز على عملي هنا.
♫Though the destiny between us is differently defined♫
♫على الرغم من أن المصير بيننا مُحدد بشكل مختلف♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫أعتقد أن حبنا سيغيرنا♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫يا قدر، أعد كتابة النبوءات♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫حتى لو كانوا ضد مصيرنا♫
♫(But we're gonna try… try… try!)♫
♫(لكننا سنحاول... سنحاول... سنحاول!)♫
Let's go. Kick your legs.
هيا بنا. حرك ساقيك.
Coach, I'm gonna head out now.
يا مدرب، سأغادر الآن.
- Bye. - Bye now.
- مع السلامة. - مع السلامة الآن.
Oh! Itthiphumi, are you forgetting your phone?
أوه! إيثيفومي، هل نسيت هاتفك؟
Uh... My phone is right here.
همم... هاتفي هنا.
Hey, double-check it.
مهلاً، تأكد من ذلك مرة أخرى.
Excuse me, that's my phone.
عفواً، هذا هاتفي.
Where are you now?
أين أنت الآن؟
Your querents are here waiting.
المستفسرون هنا في انتظاركم.
I'm not coming in tonight.
لن أدخل الليلة.
Still not caught up with my work.
لم أتمكن بعد من إنجاز جميع أعمالي.
You're scared to meet his real sweetheart?
هل تخافين من مقابلة حبيبته الحقيقية؟
Man, he's good-looking.
يا رجل، إنه وسيم.
I think that if they eventually meet...
أعتقد أنه إذا التقيا في النهاية...
Oh! Hey,
أوه! مهلاً،
what are you saying? I can't hear you.
ماذا تقول؟ لا أستطيع سماعك.
Pure, the reception is bad.
بيور، الاستقبال سيء.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Is Ritt almost here?
هل اقترب موعد وصول ريت؟
Master Ritt just bailed.
انسحب السيد ريت للتو.
What?
ماذا؟
No whats.
لا شيء.
We have never told the customers that Ritt would come in every day.
لم نخبر العملاء قط بأن ريت سيأتي كل يوم.
But you already told that new customer
لكنك أخبرت ذلك العميل الجديد بالفعل
to come to Ritt today.
أن يأتي إلى ريت اليوم.
I'm not late
أنا لست متأخراً
for today's first appointment, am I?
هل أنا جاهز لأول موعد لي اليوم؟
Uh... So...
آه... إذن...
You're not.
أنت لست.
But...
لكن...
do you mind waiting?
هل تمانع الانتظار؟
Are you in a hurry tonight?
هل أنت مستعجل الليلة؟
Why?
لماذا؟
I have a new cocktail recipe for you to try.
لدي وصفة كوكتيل جديدة لتجربها.
Are you interested?
هل أنت مهتم؟
Was that Pure calling?
هل كان ذلك نداءً من بيور؟
Mm.
مم.
But I told him
لكنني أخبرته
that I wasn't going in.
أنني لن أدخل.
Are you tired?
هل أنت متعب؟
I just want to get my work done.
أريد فقط إنجاز عملي.
I need to report a progress update with the professor tomorrow.
أحتاج إلى تقديم تقرير عن آخر المستجدات مع الأستاذ غداً.
I'll take you to meet my Grandpa and Grandma later.
سآخذك لمقابلة جدي وجدتي لاحقاً.
My family believes in superstition, feng shui, energy,
تؤمن عائلتي بالخرافات، والفينغ شوي، والطاقة.
and Chinese space layout.
وتصميم الفضاء الصيني.
There are around ten feng shui masters in our company.
يوجد في شركتنا حوالي عشرة خبراء في فنغ شوي.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I might get some insights from the experts.
قد أحصل على بعض الأفكار من الخبراء.
Grandpa and Grandma will like you
سيحبك جدك وجدتك
if you guys meet.
إذا التقيتم.
Why?
لماذا؟
Well...
حسنًا...
If I like someone,
إذا أعجبتني شخصية ما،
my parents will like them as well.
سيحبها والداي أيضاً.
You're pretty good at flirting.
أنت بارع جداً في المغازلة.
Maybe if I keep flirting,
ربما إذا واصلتُ المغازلة،
I might get to go from a childhood sweetheart
قد أتمكن من الانتقال من حبيبة الطفولة
to something real one day.
إلى شيء حقيقي يوماً ما.
If we weren't sweethearts,
لو لم نكن حبيبين،
it would've been hard to approach you, huh?
كان من الصعب الاقتراب منك، أليس كذلك؟
Just a bit.
قليلاً فقط.
I just don't have chemistry with anyone
أنا ببساطة لا أشعر بالانسجام مع أي شخص
to click with out there.
للنقر من الخارج.
Keep working.
استمر في العمل.
I'll visit again tomorrow.
سأزوركم مجدداً غداً.
Okay.
تمام.
Drive safe.
قد بأمان.
Pitcha, are you hungry? Have you eaten?
بيتشا، هل أنت جائع؟ هل تناولت طعامك؟
Would you like to order anything?
هل ترغب في طلب أي شيء؟
We serve delicious food here.
نقدم هنا طعاماً لذيذاً.
I'm good.
أنا بخير.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You have to be on a diet, right?
يجب أن تكوني ملتزمة بنظام غذائي، أليس كذلك؟
I watched Jinha's interview.
شاهدت مقابلة جينها.
They really ate so little.
لقد أكلوا القليل جداً.
When will Master Ritt be here?
متى سيصل السيد ريت؟
Oh...
أوه...
Here,
هنا،
'Oppa on the Rock.'
"أوبا على الصخرة".
I just came up with the name,
لقد اخترت الاسم للتو،
inspired by...
مستوحى من...
a Thai idol who rose to stardom overseas.
نجم تايلاندي حقق شهرة عالمية.
Better hurry and give it a taste.
من الأفضل الإسراع وتجربته.
It's one of a kind. So unique that no one can recreate it.
إنها فريدة من نوعها. فريدة لدرجة أنه لا يمكن لأحد أن يعيد صنعها.
We couldn't, even if you ask for it next time.
لا نستطيع، حتى لو طلبت ذلك في المرة القادمة.
That's too much, sis.
هذا كثير جداً يا أختي.
Give it a go.
جربها.
I'm open to feedback about the taste.
أرحب بأي ملاحظات حول المذاق.
Ugh!
أوف!
Hey!
يا!
What did you put in it? Why is it so strong?
ماذا وضعت فيه؟ ولماذا هو قويٌّ جدًّا؟
Lots of things.
أشياء كثيرة.
But the most important of all
لكن الأهم من كل ذلك
is that I poured my heart into it.
الأمر هو أنني بذلت فيه كل ما في قلبي.
That explains why it's bitter.
وهذا يفسر سبب مرارته.
Burn!
يحرق!
So...
لذا...
what is bothering you so bad
ما الذي يزعجك بشدة؟
that you want to have your fortune read with Master Ritt?
هل ترغب في قراءة طالعك مع المعلم ريت؟
- Does it hurt? - No, you're doing great.
- هل يؤلمك؟ - لا، أنت رائع.
My shins feel stiff.
أشعر بتيبس في ساقي.
Grandma.
جدتي.
You left so early and came home this late?
غادرت مبكراً جداً وعدت إلى المنزل في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
What have you been out for?
لماذا كنت بالخارج؟
Jeez...
يا إلهي...
Why are you still up, Grandma?
لماذا ما زلتِ مستيقظة يا جدتي؟
That could really age you.
هذا قد يجعلك تبدو أكبر سناً.
You haven't answered my question.
لم تجب على سؤالي.
Judging from how you act, are you dating someone?
هل أنت على علاقة عاطفية بشخص ما ، بناءً على تصرفاتك ؟
Who's that poor one unlucky enough to have you as a boyfriend?
من هي تلك المسكينة التعيسة الحظ التي يكون أنت حبيبها؟
Jeez, Grandma.
يا إلهي، يا جدتي.
They're the lucky one.
إنهم المحظوظون.
So there's really someone?
إذن، هل يوجد شخص ما حقاً؟
Is there?
هل يوجد؟
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
You look strangely cheerful these days.
تبدو سعيداً بشكل غريب هذه الأيام.
You're barely home at that.
بالكاد تكون في المنزل حينها.
If you meet them,
إذا قابلتهم،
you're gonna like them.
ستعجبك.
Really now?
حقاً؟
I want to meet them.
أريد مقابلتهم.
I wanna know what they're like. Would you bring them home?
أريد أن أعرف كيف هم. هل ستأخذهم إلى المنزل؟
You're already in a relationship.
أنت بالفعل في علاقة.
Don't be all affectionate now.
لا تكن عاطفياً جداً الآن.
Ploy,
حيلة،
that table wants their bill.
تلك الطاولة تريد دفع فاتورتها.
You go.
اذهب أنت.
You go, so you can get a tip.
اذهب أنت، حتى تحصل على بقشيش.
You're nothing like I imagined.
أنت لست كما تخيلتك على الإطلاق.
When I first saw you on the news,
عندما رأيتك لأول مرة على الأخبار،
in those videos Ploy showed me,
في تلك الفيديوهات التي أراني إياها بلوي،
I thought you were someone so perfect that you were flawless,
كنت أظن أنك شخص مثالي لدرجة أنك لا تشوبك شائبة،
down to the finest detail.
حتى أدق التفاصيل.
But when I actually see you...
لكن عندما أراك فعلاً...
You're completely different from what I thought.
أنت مختلف تماماً عما كنت أظن.
What am I like in person?
كيف أبدو في الواقع؟
You seem like an ordinary guy.
تبدو كشخص عادي.
Except that...
باستثناء ذلك...
you're good-looking
أنت وسيم
with a great body,
بجسم رائع،
great skin,
بشرة رائعة،
beautiful eyes,
عيون جميلة،
luscious hair,
شعر كثيف وجميل،
- and... - That's still ordinary, right?
- و... - هذا لا يزال أمراً عادياً، أليس كذلك؟
And...
و...
you seem more genuine than I saw in videos.
تبدو أكثر صدقاً مما رأيته في الفيديوهات.
Living there
العيش هناك
must be so draining for you.
لا بد أن الأمر مرهق للغاية بالنسبة لك.
I saw nothing but one practice video after another.
لم أرَ شيئاً سوى فيديو تدريبي تلو الآخر.
Yes,
نعم،
I trained very hard
لقد تدربت بجد
and barely got any sleep.
ولم ينم إلا قليلاً.
I have to bear the pressure every day,
عليّ أن أتحمل الضغط كل يوم،
and in the end...
وفي النهاية...
I didn't even get to debut.
لم أتمكن حتى من الظهور لأول مرة.
But you can still smile.
لكن لا يزال بإمكانك الابتسام.
Probably because if I hadn't been smiling,
ربما لأنني لو لم أكن مبتسماً،
I would’ve been on the ground by now.
كنت سأكون على الأرض الآن.
I think...
أظن...
you're a lot better than you think you are.
أنت أفضل بكثير مما تعتقد.
Or maybe...
أو ربما...
I'm only like that in front of others.
أنا أتصرف هكذا فقط أمام الآخرين.
Your eyes
عيناك
really don't hide a single thing.
لا يخفون أي شيء على الإطلاق.
Why?
لماذا؟
Whatever you feel
مهما كان شعورك
or think,
أو فكر،
I can tell when I look into your eyes.
أستطيع أن أعرف ذلك عندما أنظر في عينيك.
Let's give it a test.
لنجربها.
What do you think
ماذا تعتقد
I'm thinking?
أظن ذلك؟
Right now, you want a friend to talk to.
أنت الآن بحاجة إلى صديق تتحدث إليه.
You want someone who truly listens.
أنت تريد شخصًا يستمع إليك حقًا.
And I...
وأنا...
happen to be a good listener,
أنا مستمع جيد،
in case you don't know.
في حال كنت لا تعلم.
So... is Master Ritt still coming in?
إذن... هل سيأتي السيد ريت؟
Ploy, call Master Ritt and ask if he's almost here.
بلوي، اتصل بالسيد ريت واسأله إن كان على وشك الوصول.
Oh,
أوه،
Ritt sent a message saying he wasn't able to catch up with his work.
أرسل ريت رسالة قال فيها إنه لم يتمكن من اللحاق بعمله.
He won't be coming in anymore today.
لن يأتي اليوم.
I think you've missed him.
أعتقد أنك افتقدته.
The wait was in vain.
كان الانتظار عبثاً.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
Talking to you has been pretty fun.
لقد كان الحديث معك ممتعاً للغاية.
I...
أنا...
just happen to be a big storyteller, too,
وهو أيضاً راوي قصص بارع.
in case you don't know.
في حال كنت لا تعلم.
I won't give you any changes
لن أعطيك أي تغييرات
so that you will come back.
حتى تعود.
Consider this a prepayment.
اعتبر هذا دفعة مقدمة.
If you don't come back,
إذا لم تعد،
it's your loss.
إنها خسارتك.
Okay.
تمام.
Then...
ثم...
Please excuse me.
أرجو المعذرة.
See you again.
أراك مجدداً.
What?
ماذا؟
I saw that.
لقد رأيت ذلك.
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫وأعتقد أن لحبنا قوة♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫أؤمن بحبنا♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line where they should be♫
♫سيعيد ترتيب النجوم إلى الخط الذي ينبغي أن تكون عليه♫
Right, Itthi, since you have time,
حسناً يا إيثي، بما أن لديكِ الوقت،
come to the company with me.
تعال معي إلى الشركة.
They said there would be a new presentation for the new project.
قالوا إنه سيكون هناك عرض تقديمي جديد للمشروع الجديد.
That way, you can give me a hand.
بهذه الطريقة، يمكنك مساعدتي.
I have some chicken braised, and I'm going to make shou mian.
لدي بعض الدجاج المطهو ​​ببطء، وسأقوم بتحضير شو ميان.
Then I'll have the chauffeur deliver it to you two for lunch.
ثم سأطلب من السائق أن يوصلها لكما لتناول الغداء.
- I... - Right, and change into a suit because
- أنا... - حسنًا، وسأغير ملابسي إلى بدلة لأن
this looks way too young.
هذا يبدو أصغر من اللازم بكثير.
It has to be a distinguished look, alright?
يجب أن يكون مظهراً مميزاً، حسناً؟
Of course, Grandpa.
بالتأكيد يا جدي.
And tomorrow,
وغداً،
there will be personnel from an overseas company visiting us.
سيكون هناك موظفون من شركة أجنبية يزوروننا.
They want to have a look at the construction site.
يريدون إلقاء نظرة على موقع البناء.
There. Take Itthi with you.
ها هو ذا. خذ إيثي معك.
- He's good at the language. He could help. - Exactly.
- إنه يجيد اللغة. يمكنه المساعدة. - بالضبط.
I was going to say that.
كنت سأقول ذلك.
From now on, you can demand the salary from your grandfather.
من الآن فصاعدًا، يمكنك المطالبة بالراتب من جدك.
Don't work for him for free, alright?
لا تعمل لديه مجاناً، حسناً؟
Well, well, look at you egging him on.
حسناً، حسناً، انظر إليك وأنت تحرضه على ذلك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I have to visit the company with Grandpa. I won't be able to see you today.
عليّ زيارة الشركة مع جدي. لن أتمكن من رؤيتك اليوم.
It's fine. I was just thinking about researching at the university.
لا بأس. كنت أفكر فقط في إجراء بحث في الجامعة.
Will probably be there until dusk.
من المحتمل أن أبقى هناك حتى الغسق.
Stay focused. Don't charm anyone, or I'll get jealous.
ركّز جيداً. لا تحاول إبهار أحد، وإلا سأشعر بالغيرة.
There you go again. Is your family business real estate or professional flirting?
ها أنت ذا مجدداً. هل عمل عائلتك في مجال العقارات أم مغازلة مهنية؟
Is Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master, in today?
هل ريت، سيد حجر النبوءة، موجود اليوم؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hey! Wait.
مهلاً! انتظر.
I have a special cocktail for you today.
لدي كوكتيل مميز لك اليوم.
It's the new and improved Oppa on the Rock.
إنه أوبا أون ذا روك الجديد والمُحسّن.
Please test it for me.
أرجو منك تجربته من أجلي.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
Just a little?
قليلاً فقط؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Here you go,
ها أنت ذا،
the new and improved Oppa on the Rock.
أوبا الجديد والمُحسّن على الصخرة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Uh... On what days does Master Ritt usually come in?
همم... في أي أيام يأتي السيد ريت عادةً؟
Here,
هنا،
for a lady like you, I believe you'll enjoy the sweetness.
أعتقد أنكِ، يا سيدتي، ستستمتعين بالحلاوة.
I recommend 'Red Pomegranate,'
أوصي بـ "الرمان الأحمر".
Is Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master coming in today?
هل سيأتي ريت، سيد حجر النبوءة، اليوم؟
He hasn't shown up just yet.
لم يظهر بعد.
I actually called him,
لقد اتصلت به بالفعل،
but he didn't pick up.
لكنه لم يرد.
Anyway, would you care for a drink?
على أي حال، هل ترغب في تناول مشروب؟
Uh...
أوه...
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
But you'll give him another call, right?
لكنك ستتصل به مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
I'll give him another call.
سأتصل به مرة أخرى.
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
Can I have your number?
هل يمكنني الحصول على رقمك؟
Whenever he comes in,
كلما دخل،
I'll give you a call.
سأتصل بك.
Would you mind putting your number on my phone, Pitcha?
هل تمانعين في وضع رقمك على هاتفي يا بيتشا؟
Now, we both have each other's numbers.
الآن، أصبح لدينا أرقام بعضنا البعض.
So...
لذا...
when do you have time
متى يتوفر لديك الوقت
for me to give you a call?
هل تريد مني أن أتصل بك؟
About Master Ritt, right?
بخصوص السيد ريت، صحيح؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
And...
و...
maybe about something else, too.
ربما يتعلق الأمر بشيء آخر أيضاً.
It'd be great to know the appropriate time to call.
سيكون من الرائع معرفة الوقت المناسب للاتصال.
Anytime.
في أي وقت.
If I have time, I'll pick up.
إذا كان لدي وقت، فسأرد.
If I don't have time, I won't pick up.
إذا لم يكن لدي وقت، فلن أرد على المكالمة.
So you're saying I can call?
إذن أنت تقول أنه بإمكاني الاتصال؟
Grandpa asked me to go to the site with him.
طلب مني جدي أن أذهب معه إلى الموقع.
That's the fourth day we won't get to see each other.
هذا هو اليوم الرابع الذي لن نتمكن فيه من رؤية بعضنا البعض.
You're not using work as an excuse to ditch me, right?
أنت لا تستخدم العمل كذريعة للتخلي عني، أليس كذلك؟
Who'd ditch you? I'm missing you to death now.
من سيتخلى عنك؟ أشتاق إليك بشدة الآن.
Calculating the value of the building offered to us for sale this afternoon?
هل نقوم بحساب قيمة المبنى المعروض علينا للبيع بعد ظهر اليوم؟
I saw you multiply something by a hundred or a thousand there.
رأيتك تضرب شيئًا ما في مئة أو ألف هناك.
Uh...
أوه...
Yes, Grandpa.
نعم يا جدي.
What do you think the number should be multiplied by?
برأيك، ما هو الرقم الذي يجب ضربه؟
I think that would be...
أعتقد أن ذلك سيكون...
too little...
قليل جدًا...
Let's go with this number.
لنعتمد هذا الرقم.
My beloved buddy,
صديقي الحبيب،
could you enlighten me in regards to your whereabouts?
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني بمكان وجودك؟
You are immensely needed by the bar.
أنت مطلوب بشدة من قبل الحانة.
Uh...
أوه...
I...
أنا...
If it's about Pitcha,
إذا كان الأمر يتعلق بـ Pitcha،
I've taken care of it.
لقد تكفلت بالأمر.
How did you do that?
كيف فعلت ذلك؟
I told him that
أخبرته بذلك
if he still wants his fortune read by you,
إذا كان لا يزال يرغب في أن تقرأ له طالعه،
I'll give him a call.
سأتصل به.
That means as long as I don't, he's not gonna show up.
هذا يعني أنه طالما لم أفعل ذلك، فلن يظهر.
In short,
باختصار،
I solved your problem.
لقد حللت مشكلتك.
So would you, my dear friend,
وأنت كذلك يا صديقي العزيز.
be so kind as to grace my bar?
هل تتفضل بزيارة حانتي؟
While I was away,
أثناء غيابي،
how is the bar doing?
كيف حال البار؟
The sale dropped to some degree.
انخفضت المبيعات إلى حد ما.
That's why I'm trying everything to get you to service your fans.
لهذا السبب أحاول بكل الطرق أن أجعلك تخدم جمهورك.
I told them that you were definitely coming back,
أخبرتهم أنك ستعود بالتأكيد،
but I just didn't know when,
لكنني لم أكن أعرف متى،
and that it was all in the master's hands.
وأن الأمر كله كان في يد السيد.
Alright, alright.
حسناً، حسناً.
I've been bored lately.
أشعر بالملل مؤخراً.
Gotta go.
يجب أن أذهب.
I'm going in tonight.
سأدخل الليلة.
Thank you so much, my friend.
شكراً جزيلاً لك يا صديقي.
I myself
أنا نفسي
will prepare a nice drink to welcome you.
سأقوم بإعداد مشروب لذيذ للترحيب بكم.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
If this whole thing pans out to be good,
إذا سارت الأمور على ما يرام،
it will be obvious to your eyes.
سيكون ذلك واضحاً لعينيك.
But if it's not getting better,
لكن إذا لم يتحسن الوضع،
that means it needs fixing.
هذا يعني أنه يحتاج إلى إصلاح.
And there's no one for that but...
وليس هناك من يقوم بذلك سوى...
you!
أنت!
The one who will fix it!
الشخص الذي سيصلحها!
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
A heart...
قلب...
can't be controlled.
لا يمكن السيطرة عليه.
If they are to love, it's because they genuinely feel for you.
إذا كان من المفترض أن يحبوك، فذلك لأنهم يشعرون بك بصدق.
But if they don't,
لكن إن لم يفعلوا،
you can't force them to do anything.
لا يمكنك إجبارهم على فعل أي شيء.
See, girl? Told you so.
شفتي يا بنت؟ قلت لكِ كذا.
Do you believe me now?
هل تصدقني الآن؟
Do your best!
ابذل قصارى جهدك!
And wait to see what happens.
وانتظر لترى ما سيحدث.
If you're right for each other,
إذا كنتما مناسبين لبعضكما البعض،
you will know from how they respond.
ستعرف ذلك من خلال ردة فعلهم.
Don't rush it!
لا تتعجل!
Give yourself some time.
امنح نفسك بعض الوقت.
Do the same for them.
افعل الشيء نفسه من أجلهم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Here you go. This one is gonna be very strong.
تفضل. هذا سيكون قوياً جداً.
Is that the last one, Ployplern?
هل هذا هو الأخير يا بلويبليرن؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
That was quite a lot on your plate. They knew you came, so they all rushed in.
كان ذلك عبئاً كبيراً عليك. لقد علموا بقدومك، لذا اندفعوا جميعاً إلى الداخل.
Easy peasy.
سهل جداً.
Didn't you tell me that you'd give me a call
ألم تخبرني أنك ستتصل بي؟
if Master Ritt would come?
ماذا لو جاء السيد ريت؟
Well...
حسنًا...
how did you know he was here?
كيف عرفت أنه كان هنا؟
I saw some posts that tagged the bar.
رأيت بعض المنشورات التي أشارت إلى الحانة.
Pure,
نقي،
since I'm all done with the slots,
بما أنني انتهيت تماماً من ماكينات القمار،
I'm heading out.
سأغادر.
I'm not gonna wait for the bar to close.
لن أنتظر حتى يغلق البار.
Are you Ritt, the Prophecy Stone Master?
هل أنت ريت، سيد حجر النبوءة؟
Do you mind taking another customer?
هل تمانع في استقبال زبون آخر؟
The ceremony has finished.
انتهى الحفل.
But I looked into the astrological calendar,
لكنني اطلعت على التقويم الفلكي،
and it didn't mention any ceremony that has to be performed.
ولم يذكر أي مراسم يجب القيام بها.
It's newly emerged.
لقد ظهر حديثاً.
This ceremony will bless you with prosperity!
ستباركك هذه المراسم بالرخاء!
Yes, prosperity!
نعم، الرخاء!
The Romani art also states the same.
ويؤكد الفن الروماني أيضاً على نفس الأمر.
The Lanna said, a ceremony performed during the night
وقال اللانا إن مراسم أقيمت خلال الليل
will be favored!
سيحظى بالأفضلية!
Do I make offerings at the shrine tomorrow morning?
هل أقدم القرابين في المزار صباح الغد؟
You still have to.
لا يزال عليك القيام بذلك.
Sure, sure.
بالتأكيد، بالتأكيد.
- As for the supply and ceremony fee... - Right!
- أما بالنسبة لرسوم التوريد والحفل... - صحيح!
- Could I... - Give me the total.
- هل يمكنني... - أعطني المبلغ الإجمالي.
I'll take care of it, alright?
سأعتني بالأمر، حسناً؟
- Sure, sure. - Come on.
- بالتأكيد، بالتأكيد. - هيا بنا.
Let's go inside.
هيا ندخل.
Itthi,
إيثي،
do you have to help your grandpa at the company tomorrow?
هل عليك مساعدة جدك في الشركة غداً؟
Uh, he said that I didn't have to.
قال إنه ليس عليّ فعل ذلك.
He has a meeting with his friend about the land near Rangsit.
لديه اجتماع مع صديقه بخصوص الأرض القريبة من رانجسيت.
Well, well, I can see sparks flying from your eyes from not having to work.
حسناً، حسناً، أستطيع أن أرى شرارات تتطاير من عينيك لعدم اضطرارك للعمل.
How about this? Tomorrow,
ما رأيك بهذا؟ غداً،
would you come with me to the old market to help me carry my stuff?
هل يمكنك أن تأتي معي إلى السوق القديم لتساعدني في حمل أغراضي؟
You have three people to help you with your stuff.
لديك ثلاثة أشخاص لمساعدتك في أغراضك.
I'll sit this one out.
سأمتنع عن المشاركة في هذه المباراة.
So where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Hm?
همم؟
Why are you bugging the kid?
لماذا تزعج الطفل؟
He looks strangely lively!
يبدو نشيطاً بشكل غريب!
Are you jealous?
هل تشعر بالغيرة؟
We'd better get inside, Grandma.
من الأفضل أن ندخل إلى الداخل يا جدتي.
Alright, come on. Let's get inside.
حسناً، هيا بنا. لندخل.
Anything else you want to ask,
هل لديك أي أسئلة أخرى؟
besides your career in Korea?
إلى جانب مسيرتك المهنية في كوريا؟
There is.
هنالك.
What do you want to ask the stones about?
ما الذي تريد أن تسأل عنه الأحجار؟
Love.
حب.
Concentrate deeply.
ركز بعمق.
Set your mind on what you wish to ask.
ركز على ما ترغب في سؤاله.
These stones reveal the reality
تكشف هذه الأحجار عن الحقيقة
and settle your doubts according to...
وحسم شكوكك وفقًا لـ...
the prophecy.
النبوءة.
Close your eyes
أغمض عينيك
and pick three stones.
ثم اختر ثلاثة أحجار.
What is your query?
ما هو استفسارك؟
I want to know
أريد أن أعرف
if the person who stood by me in the past
لو أن الشخص الذي وقف بجانبي في الماضي
will return to me.
سيعود إليّ.
You should move on.
يجب أن تمضي قدماً.
He's never coming back to you.
لن يعود إليك أبداً.
Was your prediction
هل كان تنبؤك صحيحًا؟
a result of a conflict of interest?
هل كان ذلك نتيجة لتضارب المصالح؟
Within three days,
في غضون ثلاثة أيام،
there will be little omens as a warning.
ستكون هناك إشارات صغيرة بمثابة تحذير.
Ow!
آخ!
I think... I'm gonna quit fortune-telling.
أعتقد... أنني سأتوقف عن قراءة الطالع.
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
I feel like everything is getting out of hand.
أشعر أن الأمور بدأت تخرج عن السيطرة.
Can you give me a hand?
هل يمكن ان تعطيني يد؟
We're stuck inside.
نحن عالقون في الداخل.
Please open the door.
يرجى فتح الباب.
Can anybody hear me?
هل يسمعني أحد؟
♫Is it pure coincidence?♫
♫هل هي مجرد صدفة؟♫
♫Or is it destiny that decides?♫
♫أم أن القدر هو الذي يقرر؟♫
♫Is someone above drawing all these lines?♫
♫هل هناك من يرسم كل هذه الخطوط من الأعلى؟♫
♫Or playing matchmaker in disguise?♫
♫ أم أنك تلعب دور خاطبة متخفية؟ ♫
♫What if the stars shift in their place♫
♫ ماذا لو تحركت النجوم من مكانها؟ ♫
♫Slightly out of line,♫
♫خارج عن المألوف قليلاً،♫
♫Will our orbits still align?♫
♫هل ستظل مداراتنا متطابقة؟♫
♫Try answering if your world will cross with mine♫
♫ حاول الإجابة عما إذا كان عالمك سيتقاطع مع عالمي ♫
♫Though the destiny between us is differently defined♫
♫على الرغم من أن المصير بيننا مُحدد بشكل مختلف♫
♫I believe our love will change our♫
♫أعتقد أن حبنا سيغيرنا♫
♫Destiny, rewrite prophecies♫
♫يا قدر، أعد كتابة النبوءات♫
♫Even if they are against our destiny♫
♫حتى لو كانوا ضد مصيرنا♫
♫(But we're gonna try… try… try!)♫
♫(لكننا سنحاول... سنحاول... سنحاول!)♫
♫And I believe our love has power♫
♫وأعتقد أن لحبنا قوة♫
♫I believe the love of us♫
♫أؤمن بحبنا♫
♫Will realign the stars back to the line where they should be♫
♫سيعيد ترتيب النجوم إلى الخط الذي ينبغي أن تكون عليه♫
♫(And we're gonna try… try… try!)♫
♫(وسنحاول... نحاول... نحاول!)♫